As you might have done before,
你可能曾经做过这样的操作
you install Python packages using pip install.
使用 pip install 来安装 Python 软件包
For example, if you want to install the scikit-learn package you go into
比如说 如果你想要安装 scikit-learn 软件包
a terminal and type pip install scikit-learn.
你会进入终端 然后输入 pip install scikit-learn
This pip install command downloads packages from an online repository called PyPy.
pip install 命令会在 PyPI 在线存储库中下载软件包
In this case, scikit-learn is already installed so it's just letting you know.
在这个示例中 scikit-learn 已经安装了 所以命令只会告知一下
In the remaining parts of this lesson,
在这节课的剩余部分
you're going to set up a Python package and then upload the package to PyPy.
你将构建一个 Python 软件包并将其上传到 PyPI 中
The first step is to get the package ready so that it
首先需要先将软件包准备好
can be pip installed locally on your computer.
使其可以在本地使用 pip 安装
I'm going to show you how to set up your files so that they can be pip installed.
我将展示一下如何设置文件才可以被 pip 安装
On the left-hand side of the screen,
在屏幕的左手边
you can see I'm in a directory containing a folder called
可以看到我现在所在目录中包含
Distributions and a file called setup.py.
distributions 文件夹和 setup.py 文件
Let's talk about the distributions folder first.
先来看一下 distributions 文件夹
Double-clicking, this folder contains
双击打开 这个文件夹包含了
the Gaussian and general distribution classes that you've already been working with.
之前编写的高斯分布和通用分布类
The difference is that this folder is now officially
区别在于 现在这个文件夹是一个正式的 Python 软件包了
a Python package because the folder contains an init file.
因为现在文件夹中包含了一个 init 文件
A package needs an init file.
软件包需要一个 init 文件
There's nothing new or different about the Gaussian and general distribution files except
与之前的高斯分布和通用分布文件相比 只有一行代码存在差异
for one line, opening Gaussian distributions.py.
打开 Gaussiandistributions.py 文件
You can see the third line where I import
可以看到第三行
the distribution class from the general distribution.py file.
我导入了 Generaldistribution.py 文件中的 Distribution 类
There's a dot in front of general distribution.
在 Generaldistribution 之前多了一个点
This.is required in Python three but
这个点是 Python3 的要求
if you're working in Python two you shouldn't need it.
如果你使用的是 Python2 则不需要
The init Python file on the other hand is new.
另一方面 init 是新添加的文件
The init file is telling Python that this folder contains a package.
init 文件告诉 Python 这个目录中包含了一个软件包
A package always needs to have an init file even if the file is completely empty.
软件包必须要包含 init 文件 即使该文件中完全空白
The code inside the init file gets run
init 文件中的代码会在
whenever you import a package inside a Python program.
你导入该软件包时运行
In this case, the init file is importing
在这个案例中 init 文件
the Gaussian class from the Gaussian distribution module.
从 Gaussiandistribution 模块中导入了 Gaussian 类
The reason I added this line is because I want to be able to import the Gaussian class
添加这行代码是因为 我想要通过编写 from distributions import Gaussian 代码
directly writing from distributions import Gaussian.
就能直接导入 Gaussian 类
You'll see what I mean in a bit.
你将在稍后了解这句话的意思
If I didn't include any code in the init file,
如果我没有在 init 文件中包括任何代码
the package would still work but any program that
软件包仍然可以正常运行 但是任何使用该包的程序
uses the package would have to import the Gaussian class more
导入 Gaussian 类都会更麻烦
indirectly with the line from distributions.Gaussian distribution import Gaussian.
需要编写代码 from distributions.Gaussiandistribution import Gaussian
It's like I'm making a shortcut for importing the Gaussian class directly.
这就像创建了一个直接导入 Gaussian 类的快捷方式
Going back up one level in the directory,
回到目录的上一级
there's a setup.py file at the same level as the distribution folder.
与 distributions 同级的目录中包含了一个 setup.py 文件
This file is necessary for pip installing.
这个文件是 pip 安装所必需的
Pip will automatically look for this file.
pip 会自动查找该文件
Opening this file, you can see the setup file
打开文件 你会看到其中
contains information or metadata about the package,
包含了软件包的信息或元数据
like the package name,
比如包名
version, description, et cetera.
版本 描述等等
Let's install the package.
我们开始安装这个软件包吧!
To install the package,
要安装该包
go into a terminal and make sure you're in the directory with the setup.py file.
先进入终端 确保你所在的目录是 setup.py 文件所在目录
In this case, I'm going to have to change directories and type python package example.
在这个示例中 我需要修改目录 输入 cd python_package_example
Now I'm in the directory containing the distributions package and the setup.py file.
现在我就在包含 distributions 软件包和 setup.py 文件的目录中了
In the terminal, type pip install.
在终端中 输入 pip install .
and then hit enter. The dot tells pip to look for the setup file in the current folder.
然后点击回车 这个点告诉 pip 在当前目录下查找 setup 文件
That's it. The Python package is installed.
搞定 Python 软件包安装好了
Now I can use the package in my Python code like so.
现在我可以在我的 Python 代码中使用该软件包了
I'm going to open a new terminal.
我要打开一个新的终端
Notice that I'm no longer in
注意 我现在已经不在
the Python package example folder and it doesn't
python_package_example 目录下
matter because we've already installed the package.
这没关系 因为我们已经安装好了软件包
So, I'm going type Python to start
输入 python 进入
the Python interpreter and then I'm going to import the Gaussian class saying,
Python 解释器 然后导入 Gaussian 类
from distributions import Gaussian, and hitting enter.
输入 from distributions import Gaussian 然后点击回车
Now, I have access to the Gaussian class so I can write something like,
现在我可以访问 Gaussian 类 所以可以写这样的代码
gaussian_one equals gaussian class
gaussian_one = Gaussian(10,5)
and initialize it with a mean of 10 and a standard deviation of five.
使用均值 10 和标准偏差 5 来初始化该分布
Hit Enter and now look,
点击回车 现在看到
I can use the Gaussian class just like
我可以像之前的方式一样
we were using it before and you have access to all the methods as well.
使用 Gaussian 类了 你也可以访问其中的所有方法
So, you might ask yourself,
你可能会问
where exactly did the package get installed to?
这个安装包到底安装在哪里了?
The answer is wherever pip installs packages on your system.
答案就是 你的系统中 pip 安装软件包的位置
If you're still in a Python interpreter and
如果你仍然在 Python 解释器中
type import package like, import distributions,
输入导入软件包的代码比如 import distributions
you can then type distributions to underscore underscore file underscore underscore,
你可以输入 distributions.__file__
hit enter and that'll tell you where the package is installed.
点击回车 这将打印出软件包安装的位置
That's all it takes to create and install a Python package locally.
这就是本地创建 Python 软件包以及本地安装的全过程
In the last part of the course,
在这节课的最后一部分
you're going to expand this package creating a binomial distribution class.
你将扩展该软件包 创建一个二项分布类
Then you can upload the package to PyPy so
然后你可以将软件包上传到 PyPI
that anybody can download and install your package.
这样所有人都可以下载并安装你的软件包
If you decide to install this package on your local computer,
如果你决定在本地计算机上安装这个软件包
you might want to create something called a virtual environment first.
你应该要先创建一个虚拟环境
A virtual environment is like a silo for installing Python packages.
虚拟环境就好像是一个用来安装 Python 软件包的孤岛
That way you won't be messing around with your computer's default Python installation.
这样你就不会影响到计算机的默认 Python 安装
I'll put instructions on the next page for setting up a virtual environment.
我会在下一页给出设置虚拟环境的说明